- Previously
on "The Rookie"...
- Detective Harper.
did you tell my client
I will find a way to hang
these murders around your neck
and lock you away forever?
- As an officer of the court.
I have no choice
but to report your conduct
with Glasser
to Internal Affairs.
- You should go to D.C.
- John--
- No. I mean it.
We are strong enough
to navigate the separation.
and you really want it.
- 7-Adam-15
and Adam-300 to monitor.
10-67 in the alley
at 4th and Cole.
Woman covered in blood.
pounding on doors.
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
- 7-Adam-15. code six.
Any more information
from the 911 call?
- No. just a bloody woman
in distress.
Guys. we got blood here.
- Adam-300.
requesting additional units.
- Copy that. Adam-300.
Additional units en route.
No!
- Easy. easy.
Got you.
Get the med kit!
- Request RA. Female victim.
multiple stab wounds.
- Copy.
- You'll be all right.
We have an ambulance
on the way.
- Jordyn.
- Jordyn?
Is that who hurt you?
- Jordyn.
- Adam-300. be advised
that van is involved.
- Control. we have
another victim in a van.
- Hey. I--I'm sorry for
inviting myself over like this.
- No. no. no. no.
James has the school run
this morning. so I'm all good.
- Thank you.
- Show me.
- So Jordyn Sharpe.
Courtney Sutton.
best friends
since Palms Middle School.
No criminal records.
no fixed address.
Jordyn's parents say that
they were taking a year off
to do the whole van life thing.
trying to chart a path
post-college.
- Is there an early theory
on why they were brutalized?
- According to Border Control.
they were going
back and forth to Baja. Mexico.
Six times just this year.
- So drug mules?
- Yeah.
- Pretty girls
with clean records.
That is a cartel's dream.
Border Patrol
just waves them through.
- Yeah. I mean. young women
like this with the confidence
to just go out into the world
and deal with whatever
it hands them.
they're usually pretty naive
about the world.
I know I was.
- Hold up.
You were #VanLife?
- I dropped out of grad school
and took a little bit of time
to find myself.
- Huh.
- I spent nine months
showering outdoors
and eating roadside burritos.
- Mm. OK. we are gonna put
a pin in that conversation.
Any clue on who they
could be muling for?
- You know. there are
social media posts.
Where is it?
Yeah. OK.
It said that they spent
a lot of time in Scorpion Bay.
- That is Costa Sangre's
territory.
Well. that explains
the brutality of the murders.
Cartel was trying
to send a message.
- I mean. but why?
- Could be a dozen reasons.
They screwed up. they stole.
they were in the wrong place
at the wrong time.
- Nyla. defensive wounds
like this?
They fought like hell
to survive.
I mean.
the last thing Courtney did
was try to just
get her friend help.
It's--
I know they made mistakes.
but they did not deserve
to die like this.
This is crazy.
- No. they didn't.
- I want in on this.
- Yeah?
- And you
charged your headphones?
- Yes.
- And you remembered
to pack everything?
- Yep.
- Your night guard?
- Nope. Oh. gosh.
- And contact lens solution.
- Dang it!
How did you know
exactly what I'd forget?
- You've never once remembered
in all our travels.
- Really?
- Yeah.
I've learned to ask
for contact lens solution
in four languages.
- Are you gonna do OK?
- Yeah. I'm fine.
We are gonna be fine.
- We're gonna be
better than fine.
This is a trial run.
It's five days.
I'm gonna go look
for an apartment.
meet the new team.
I'm not moving-moving
until the end of the month.
The car is here.
I gotta go.
I love you.
- I love you.
Here you go.
- OK.
Bye.
- Bye.
- No. it's a nonstarter.
Look. you want to call
down the wrath of God
on Costa Sangre in LA.
I'm all-in.
But an undercover op
with Lucy in Mexico?
Forget it.
We got no jurisdiction.
- TID found a cigarette pack
in the weeds under the van.
Mexican packaging.
And the girls don't smoke.
- Finding a pack
of Mexican cigarettes in LA
is not out of the ordinary.
- Yeah. but there are
other key forensics
that also point to Mexico.
And the murders were gruesome.
even for the cartel.
If that was done by a local.
the streets would be buzzing.
and I have heard nothing.
I don't need your buy-in.
I need your support
to go to Grey.
I hear the Monica Task Force
is targeting Costa Sangre's
boss. Rogelio Zambada.
- OK. those women were
low-level drug mules.
You're gonna have to climb
two miles of food chain
to get to Zambada.
And why isn't Lucy here
with you pushing for this?
- She wants this approved
on its merits
without the girlfriend factor.
But she will use it
if you say no to me.
Have you heard back from IA?
- I got my notice of intent.
but the hearing
has not been scheduled.
And if you are implying
that I'm using this
as a way to delay my showdown
with Internal Affairs--
- No. I'm wondering why
you're spearheading the mission
when you made it very clear
over the last four years
that you were done
with long-term undercover work
after it pretty much
destroyed your life.
- When I was working undercover
with the cartels.
I knew so many girls
that either ended up missing
or dead.
and nobody cared.
If IA takes my badge.
at least I know
that I spent the last
of my time here
trying to get justice
for these two women.
- OK.
That's my answer.
- So you'll support us
going to the task force?
- Yeah.
- And?
- And I will find the resources
to cover it.
But none of this matters
if Grey
says--
- No.
Zambada's not
a front burner target.
And even if I believe
that you had a shot
at getting close to him.
Garza's not going to divert
focus from our current targets.
- He will if you ask him.
Sir. if you don't say yes.
we both know that these murders
will go unsolved.
- Careful. Sergeant.
I've seen plenty of tragedy
on this job.
I don't need a lecture
on justice.
- With all due respect. sir.
I--
you--you have never
been these girls.
You have never experienced
the particular type of pain
and fear that
they went through.
how brave they had to be
to go out into the world
knowing how treacherous it is
simply because they're female.
And yeah. how that bravery
and naivete caused them to be
vulnerable to the cartel.
I--I'm not excusing
their criminality.
I just--
it shouldn't have cost them
their lives.
- When you're looking back
on your deathbed--
y--no. sorry.
Sir. the politics
and the bureaucracy of this
will not matter.
What will matter is that
you stood up for these women.
- Well...
So much for not lecturing me.
OK. let's say I'm on board.
What's this gonna cost
the task force?
- Very little.
Tim can get us the funding
and the physical resources.
The only thing we need
is one FBI agent
to give the op legitimacy
with the Mexican government.
preferably someone
who speaks Spanish.
- What?
- So Bailey on her way to D.C.?
- Yeah. her flight
left 20 minutes ago.
- So you won't mind
if I loan you to Lopez
for a surveillance assignment.
- No. whatever she needs.
- All right. we're good.
You want to fill them in?
- Sure.
Man of the hour
is Keshaun DeMarco.
otherwise known as Hamster.
but don't let
the cute nickname fool you.
Keshaun has an affinity
for brute force trauma
that he's parlayed into a
growing leg-breaking business.
- Last week.
he assaulted two witnesses
in a RICO case I'm trying.
Almost caused a mistrial.
- We have a warrant
for his arrest.
but he's gone off the grid.
I got round-the-clock
surveillance authorized
on several of his haunts.
I need you
and your rookie to post up
outside his baby mama's house.
Kennedy Stowe.
- Whoa.
- Try not to let
the impressive front porch
distract you from the fact that
Kennedy threw
a classmate through a window
in high school.
She's hot and dangerous.
- Officer Penn.
this assignment could last
until you're scheduled
to graduate the FTO program.
You'll be under a microscope
until it's complete.
- Yes. sir.
Won't let you down.
Six hours.
No one's come in or out.
- Well. if Hamster
was easy to find.
Lopez wouldn't have
half the station on it.
You know. quit looking
for the hot mama sighting
and widen your focus
a little bit.
It'll give your eyes a rest
and you'll learn
about the neighborhood.
- That's a roll call.
It looks like random letters
and numbers.
but it's a list
of gang members.
The numbers stand for letters
in the alphabet.
- Exactly.
Simple code. but it can
give you a lot of information.
- Most of the numbers up there
are 14 and 2.
14 for N.
2 for B means Noho Boys.
Hamster's gang.
- Exactly.
Means he feels safe here.
He feels he's amongst friends.
- So he'll be back.
In Sugarland. I knew things.
Like if you saw Misty Foreman
packing up the kids
to take to her mother's.
meant her husband. Karl.
was dealing again.
But it's different here.
So much going on at once.
I--I feel like
I'm running behind.
I keep thinking I should hit
some neighborhood hangouts
in my off-hours.
You know. keep a low profile
and get a better feel
for what's--what's going on.
- OK. that's a bad idea.
Not only is it
inherently unsafe.
but it's against regulations.
Don't go policing
in your off-duty hours.
All right.
Relief is here.
- I'll do a deep dive into
the Noho Boys database tonight.
- Great.
I'm gonna make a cheesesteak
and watch "Commando."
two things Bailey hates.
- El Mezquital campsite.
This is where
Courtney and Jordyn
spent their time in Baja.
- I pulled previous
satellite imagery
for the last six months.
There's obviously a lot
of camper turnover.
but a few of the vehicles have
been there the whole time.
- Understood.
Receipts from Jordyn's van
show that they bought Ozempic
from a local farmacia
and sold it across the border
for a hefty profit.
We think this is
how the cartel targeted them
as potential mules.
- So we'll follow
in their footsteps.
Hopefully. they'll see us
as equally easy targets.
- Great.
Let's talk undercover personas.
- The bureau cyber unit
has the ability
to launch social media pages
for each of you
that appear to go back
over several years.
- And they will hold up
to a metadata check?
- Yeah.
- Score.
- All right.
so I have one.
My name is Xia Sun.
but I go by Shy.
I was born in Chicago.
I went to Kansas City
Art Institute.
where I got a degree
in fiber arts.
I sold a couple of pieces.
but I realized
that there wasn't much money
to be had in textile sculpture.
I met the love of my life
two years ago.
and we've been joined
at the hip ever since.
- And I am that love
of her life. Avery Reid.
I was raised in Alaska
but hated
every frigid moment of it.
so I left
and went to California
at the age of 18
and never looked back.
- Surfing is my passion.
I work odd jobs. but never
really wanted a career.
I just wanted enough cash
to chase the endless summer.
- It'll be four weeks.
Minimum. I--
- I don't know.
You just moved in.
I mean. i-it's like
you're already moving out.
- You could think of it
as an excuse
to play your video games
at full volume all weekend.
- OK. you make my life
sound so empty.
- No. no. no. no.
OK. OK.
How about this?
The longer I'm gone.
the happier you'll be
when I come back.
Hmm?
- Mm.
- Hey. sweetie.
Mommy's gotta go now.
- OK.
Leah.
- Yes?
- Remember Mommy said
I was gonna have to leave
for a little while?
- You'll be back?
- I will be back. yes.
as soon as I can. OK?
- OK.
- I love you.
- Mommy. more juice. please.
- OK.
Can you?
- Yeah.
- Thank you.
What are you drawing?
- One.
- Hey.
Hey. the van is gassed up
and ready to go.
- OK. let's do this.
- I'll let you guys
say goodbye.
- I want you to know
it is a tribute
to your excellent mothering
that she is so secure.
- OK.
- You got this.
- I love you.
- I love you too.
- All right. come on.
- I know. I know.
It'll be worth it.
- OK.
- You ready?
- Yeah.
- Lord. I wish we had
something to do out here.
- You keep drinking
all that coffee.
you'll have something to do.
all right.
Why are you so tired. anyway?
- I've been up nights studying.
trying to get inside
Hamster's world.
- This could be him.
7-Adam-15.
Possible suspect sighting.
Send backup
to 3200 Falk Drive.
- Hey.
- That's him.
- Let him get inside.
- Cop! Run!
- Stop! Police! LPD!
He's running!
- 7-Adam-15.
foot and vehicle pursuit.
Eastbound over fences
behind 3200 Falk Drive.
Suspect all in black.
- Hey!
Suspect heading south
toward Santa Monica Boulevard.
- Suspect entering
Beachwood Car Wash!
Whoa!
- Where'd he go?
- How the hell should I know?
You're the one
who had eyes on him.
- I don't know how--
how I lost him.
He was right in front of me.
then--
- Why did you go in after him?
You should have just held
the perimeter on the back side.
- I know.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
- All right. Jen. you guys.
backtrack where we came from.
see if you can track him down.
You guys circle around
the back side of the building.
I'm gonna wait out here
in the front.
7-Adam-15. we're code 4.
suspect unaccounted for.
Get in the car. Bubbles.
- Forget police tactics.
It's a failure of common sense.
- Yes. sir.
There's no excuse.
- Maybe if you hadn't been
burning the midnight oil
playing Noho catch-up.
you could have focused better.
- And now Hamster
knows we're up on his spots.
he's gonna burrow
deeper underground.
I should ask Harper
to keep an eye out for him
in case he makes a run
for Mexico.
- Man. I used to love this.
Heading into the great unknown
after I bailed on grad school.
Suddenly. it was like
anything could happen.
Life was just pure possibility.
- Why did you drop out?
- OK. so one day.
I was talking to a professor
about career paths.
and suddenly my heart
just started beating so fast.
I couldn't breathe.
I had no idea
what was going on.
- You were having
a panic attack.
- Yeah. it felt like somebody
had turned the lights on.
and I could see all of my
choices in this entire chain.
And--and at the start.
my parents were
just acting like
if I didn't get
an advanced degree.
I would end up homeless.
- So two Dr. Chens
weren't enough?
They wanted three?
- Five. actually.
- Ooh.
- My--my dad's parents
were doctors too.
- Really?
- Anyways. that panic attack
made me realize
that I hadn't ever really
made a choice for myself.
I was just always doing
what they wanted.
so yeah. I--I bailed.
- Yeah. you know.
I had issues with my parents.
but they always only
ever wanted me to be me.
and all I wanted was
to be a cop.
- You know. Nyla. I know
about the IA investigation.
If you want to--
- Yeah.
that is Nyla's business.
You--you know what Avery
is focused on?
- Sick swells and cold beer?
Yes.
- And finding the next song in
our perfect road trip playlist.
- Ooh.
- Yeah.
- Are you ready. Avery?
- Ready. Shy.
- Ooh.
Oh. wow.
It's so nice here.
Why haven't
we come here before?
- Hey. new faces.
I like it.
I'm Chase.
- Hi. Avery.
She's Shy.
- Hey.
- Shy?
Hope not.
What brings you to Baja?
- Hello.
- I mean. it's gorgeous.
- I feel that.
- I thought you said
we'd be able to hear them.
- One sec.
Shotgun mic needs fine-tuning.
- Well. you came
to the right place.
Perfect beach break.
- Do you surf?
- You know. mostly I fall.
But I keep trying. though.
- Juarez. check in.
- You know.
when I volunteered for this.
I thought I was gonna be
Nolan and Bailey in Prague.
not me in a ditch
fighting a losing battle
against bugs and snakes.
- Yeah. well. you should
have read the fine print.
- Yeah.
- So anyway.
it's a pretty chill group.
but if anyone
gives you trouble.
just let me know.
- We will. Thank you.
- Yeah.
- Thank you.
- Oh. we do a drum circle
by the fire every night.
You should join.
- Great.
- That sounds fun.
- Really?
- I mean. for Avery.
You're gonna hate it.
- Yeah. I am.
- Dude.
I am too close to graduation
to mess up this badly.
I--I gotta make it right.
- By doubling down
on your screw-up?
Trust me. I am the poster child
for that kind of behavior.
and that.
that is the wrong way to go.
Just own your mistake.
Save going rogue until it's
harder to get fired for it.
- Rogue?
It's not going rogue.
- It's kind of going rogue.
- It's just some unpaid OT
watching a baby mama all night.
- What's in it for me?
- Other than the satisfaction
of helping a friend?
OK. if something comes from it.
I'll cut you in on the credit.
It'll help smooth your path
back into the FTO program.
- And what if it all
goes wrong?
- Then you were never there.
Easy.
- OK.
Cheers.
- Cheers.
That's the house.
- Do you really think this guy
Hamster's gonna be coming back?
- Nope.
But I'm hoping she'll get
a late-night booty call
and lead us straight to him.
- I can't sleep.
- Yeah. me neither.
- You did this for fun
for nine months?
- Worse--I lived
in a hatchback.
so I actually had to pitch
a tent every single night.
Yeah. James wants to go
on a family camping trip.
and I am just not sure
that our marriage
can survive that.
- Well. after everything you
guys went through last year.
I feel like you guys
are pretty battle-tested.
- Mm. yeah.
You know. I was still
scared to tell James
that I screwed up so badly
with the Glasser case.
- Did he lecture you
about policing?
- No. worse--
he was completely on my side.
- But you wanted to fight?
Jeez.
- You know. it's easier
to defend yourself
if you're being attacked.
but there is no defending
telling someone
you're gonna hang the case
around their neck
when you have no evidence.
- Nyla. he's a serial killer.
- Yeah. and he might
get away with it
because I let my emotions
get in the way.
- Wesley's got this.
- Oh. well...
- Glasser's going to prison
for a very long time.
- I hope so.
- I think
I'm getting good at this.
- You actually do look like
you know what you're doing
and you would
be really good at this.
- Stupid.
- Who is this guy?
- You know. I might keep
my Etsy shop open
when this is done.
I think jewelry making is good
for my mental health.
- Mm-hmm.
Oh. it looks like
we might have a nibble.
- Hola. pretty ladies.
- ¿Cómo estás?
- Bien. bien.
You girls are new
at the campsite. right?
- Yeah.
- Are you guys getting this?
- I am Avery.
This is Shy.
- I don't recognize him
from the campsite.
- Shy?
- Could be cartel.
- Yeah. it's short for Xia.
- We see him.
- Xia. it's Chinese.
- Cool.
This jewelry is beautiful.
Do you sell those?
- Mostly up north.
There's a farmers market
in Malibu.
- Lots of rich people out there
to buy from you. right?
- Yeah.
- Rafael "Rafa" Navarro.
Mid-level lieutenant
for Costa Sangre.
- Did I see you girls last
week at the farmacia in town?
- It's possible
we were over there.
- Huh.
Maybe jewelry
is not the only thing
you sell to rich ladies
in Malibu.
- Listen.
we're not doing anything wrong.
- No. of course not.
We're all allowed
to earn a living. right?
It's your time. your effort.
your ability
to buy cheap Ozempic here
and sell it for three times
as much in the States.
Look. to be honest.
I do the same thing.
Come on.
Everyone here does it.
Only that...
I can't make it
across the border this week.
Would you girls be interested
in taking my shopping with you?
Come on. I can even
have a friend
meet you
to collect the pharma.
- I--I don't know.
I mean. we just do it to afford
our lifestyle. you know.
- Of course. yes. and I'll be
more than happy to contribute.
Let's say $1.500 U.S.
Hmm?
Come on.
- We could get
that laser welder.
- Yeah?
Yeah?
- Yeah.
- OK.
- Excellent. excellent.
See. I told you.
nothing illegal.
Just some local.
low-price medicine to resell.
There is a number in the box.
Just call it when you land
in Los Angeles.
and my friend come pick it up.
- Bye. girls.
- Bye.
- Did you see the--
- Cigarettes?
Yeah.
You think he's the one that
killed Jordyn and Courtney?
- Could be.
Maybe they tried to break free.
but he couldn't take the risk
they'd tell someone
and blow up
his whole operation.
All right. let's get moving.
We'll coordinate
the handoff surveillance
with Tim on the way.
- Not a word.
- I would never.
Oh. but. Tim?
- I hate you.
- I know.
- This is Alpha unit.
They're landing.
- Copy.
Harper and Lucy are landing.
Here we go.
- They're being filmed.
Blue SUV.
- Copy.
Alpha unit says the swap's
being filmed by the blue SUV.
Silver sedan
is exiting the parking lot.
Follow units.
they're all yours.
- Welcome to Astro Burger.
Can I take your order?
- No. but I've got
something else you can take.
I'm a sucker
for a man in uniform.
- Easy.
- We're on to the guys
that you gave Rafa's drugs to
and the blue car
recording the exchange.
- To blackmail us.
That means
we'll be making a trip
for the hardcore drugs next.
- Any clarity on who killed
Jordyn and Courtney?
- Maybe.
- No.
- Our cartel contact
smokes the brand
we found at the murder scene.
- That's pretty weak.
- Yeah. I know.
- All right. back to it.
That'll be $10.70.
- Thank you.
See you soon.
- I'll be here.
- Dude. Miles.
Miles.
- Mm?
- It's been two weeks. man.
How much longer
are we gonna do this?
- You're already
going above and beyond.
You can tap out anytime.
- I'm not gonna
leave you out here alone.
But this has--this has
gotta be the last night.
Dude. you're--
you're exhausted.
And you're pulling double duty.
The last thing that
you want to have happen
is things go sideways on the
job because you're a zombie.
- You're right.
And I appreciate you
for looking out.
- And don't get me wrong.
this has been really fun.
feeling relevant again
and the whole thing.
That being said. I gotta pee.
You want anything
from 7-Eleven?
- God. no.
Come on. man. where you at?
- You spying on my girl?
- Nah. man. I'm just...
looking for bats.
But it's not a problem.
I--I--I--I'll just dip.
- How dumb do you think I am?
You're the cop that chased me
through the car wash.
Get your ass out.
Reach for a piece.
they'll be picking brains
out of the upholstery
for weeks.
- All right. all right.
- Where's your gun?
- It's under my jacket.
- Take it out the holster.
Throw it into the gutter.
carefully.
- I can't leave a loaded gun
on the street.
- It's that.
or I'll leave it there
attached to your dead body.
Now your phone.
- We're gonna go
for a little ride.
- What are you doing?
- Getting rid of your problem.
- You can't kill a cop.
- Is he really dead
if you never find a body?
- Baby. you just can't--
this is crazy.
Baby. this is crazy.
- Stop arguing.
- Seth. what's going on?
- Miles is in trouble.
- Where is he?
- We're outside
of Kennedy's house.
Hamster came back.
and he's got Miles.
- What is he doing
at Kennedy's house?
What are you doing there?
- I--
- No. never mind.
Just--
I'm on my way.
Do not engage.
- 911. What's your emergency?
- This is Officer John Nolan.
I'm calling to report
a kidnapping in progress.
- Go back in the house. girl.
You called me out here.
What you think
was gonna happen?
- Baby. this is crazy.
- Stop arguing.
I'll call you in a couple weeks
when the heat dies down.
Give me a kiss.
You got your cuffs on you?
- Yeah.
- Cuff yourself.
- Be smart here. Keshaun.
Killing a cop ain't it.
- Get in. slide across.
Say another word.
I'll knock out your fronts.
- Hurry your ass up. man.
- Stay down.
- Get down.
- Hands behind your head.
- Hands where we can see them.
- OK. you got him?
- The baby mama's in on it.
- Let's get you out of here.
- We're code 4.
Stay down!
- You OK?
- Yeah. man. you saved my life.
- No problem. man.
- Need an RA unit
at the in-progress kidnapping.
We're code 4.
- He all right?
- He got his bell rung.
Nothing life-threatening.
- Good. I don't have
to wait to yell at him.
- Sir--
- Shut up.
You were doing
off-the-books surveillance
on a violent felon and you
brought Ridley. a civilian?
- Wait. sir--
- No one's talking to you.
Go to the hospital.
get checked out.
When you're finished.
you get back to the station
and clean out your locker.
You're done.
- What were you thinking?
- Oh. God.
Oh.
Ugh.
- Hey. that was
a quick turnaround.
- Yeah. well.
when paradise calls.
- Baja is like a siren song.
That's what I always say.
- And I am back in the ditch.
- How long do you think before
Rafa makes contact again?
- Day or two.
Or now.
Heads up.
- Yeah. I see him.
- Hey. watch out for that guy.
Bad news.
- Hey. take a walk.
Gotta talk to the girls.
- Yeah. no problem.
- Thank you.
Come on. girls. let's go.
Welcome back.
Mm? Any trouble?
- No. It was good.
- Glad to hear it.
I need you to make another run.
Right now.
and a bigger package.
- Thanks but no. thanks.
- That was a one-time thing.
I mean. we're set now.
- Wrong.
Unless you want LAPD
to see this.
you girls work for me now.
- You would--
you wouldn't do that.
Those are your--your men.
- They're expendable.
Got a dozen more waiting
in the wings.
- No. we--we can't.
- It's no different
than last time.
You'll get waved through the
border and meet my guys in LA.
- OK. but there--
there has to be a better way.
- No. no.
there's no better way.
There's no other way.
Open up the back.
- Look at this.
Remember how I said
there were a few vehicles
that never left the campsite?
When we landed here.
I asked Border Control
to run all the license plates.
and Rafa didn't kill the girls.
This was taken three hours
after we found Jordyn
and Courtney's bodies.
Chase was crossing
back into Mexico.
- All right. you know what?
That's enough.
Get your asses in gear.
We're gonna follow you
to the border
to make sure
you don't chicken out.
What are you doing?
I'm talking to you.
- Hi. Dad.
I--
- Daughter. Chase killed
Jordyn and Courtney.
How you want to play this?
- Give me a minute.
Let me just talk to my
girlfriend for one second.
and we will go after that. OK?
- Hey.
- Chase killed the girls.
- What?
- He must be working
for a cartel.
Maybe Rafa?
I say we hold on arresting him
and make the drug run to LA.
- What? N--no.
- This is major weight.
which will make
for a bigger arrest
on the other side.
- No. Nyla. the whole point
of us coming down here
was to get
those two women justice.
It is the only thing
that matters. right?
- You're right.
You're right.
I'm sorry. I--
- No. don't apologize.
I got you. OK?
- Come on. Hey. let's go.
Hurry up.
- Sorry. yeah.
OK. yeah.
- Celina.
we are closing the door.
- Please--
- I hope you're ready.
- We can't do this.
I'm sorry.
Come on! Please!
- And I'm out of the ditch.
- Police!
Get on the ground!
- Policía.
Manos arriba. Policía.
- Put your hands on your head.
- Don't move!
- Wow. that was unexpected.
- Yeah. you like that?
- Yeah.
you're gonna love this.
Get your hands up on that van
right now.
- What?
- Chase. you're under arrest
for the murder of Jordyn Sharpe
and Courtney Sutton.
- What?
You think we're here
just to amuse ourselves
with the local drug trade?
We're here to get justice
for the two women
that you murdered.
- Wait. hold on.
- Arms behind your back.
- I didn't kill anyone.
The crew I--
- The crew you what?
- I'm just a spotter
for a rival gang.
I tell them when Costa Sangre's
moving a big package into LA.
and they steal it.
I never leave this beach!
- He's lying.
We have you on camera
at the border
coming to Mexico from their
murders with blood on you.
They should have
just let us rob them.
But they fought back.
ripped my mask off.
I didn't want to do it.
but I didn't have a choice.
They'd have given me up.
- Don't look at me.
Don't look at me.
Can somebody
get him out of here?
- I'm s--I'm sorry.
- No need.
Grey and Elena have it handled.
- Yeah.
- We can just hang out here.
watch the water.
and feel our feelings.
- Miles. hold on.
- Sorry.
I wasn't in the mood
to say goodbye.
- Good. 'cause you'll only
be gone for two weeks.
- What?
- In the light of day.
I convinced Sergeant Bradford
to adjust your punishment.
Two weeks administrative leave.
followed by a six-month
extension in the program.
- Sir. thank you.
- Don't get too excited.
A six-month extension
is severe.
It'll be a significant
black mark on your record.
one that'll hamper
your career choices
moving forward
in the department.
- I understand.
And I truly appreciate
you going to bat for me.
- I wouldn't do it if I didn't
think you were worth it. Miles.
You have the skills.
You know the job.
What you lack
is the confidence.
Acting like a cowboy.
that's just a cover.
Deep down. you worry
that you're not worthy.
You think everyone else
sees it the same way.
The only one who can
change that mindset is you.
So I bought you six months.
Convince us you have
the maturity needed.
- Yes. sir.
I--I won't let you down.
- I know.
See you in two weeks.
- Two weeks.
- Here we are.
Home away from home.
Nyla. hey. thank you for
letting me do this with you.
- Are you kidding?
You were
the perfect girlfriend.
Right back at you.
- Aw.
- Hey. everything's
gonna be all right.
You're too good of a cop
for IA to cut.
- I hope you are right.
But thank you for saying that.
- Yeah.
- You see who it is?
- Hi. baby.
Hi.
- Mom!
- You OK?
- Yeah.
Just back to reality.
- You know. whatever happens.
they cannot take away
who you are.
- Mm.
- They definitely can't
take away what we've built.
OK?
I love you too.
No. no.
- At one point.
Jean-Claude Van Damme
floats above the scene
and delivers
a six-minute monologue.
- And this is a good movie?
- It's a perfect movie.
- OK. if you say so.
then I'm in.
Miles.
- Hey. you're back.
- Yeah.
You OK?
I'm--I wasn't fired.
- That was on the table?
- Yeah.
- OK. what happened?
- I--I really messed up.
Celina.
- Oh. I'm sorry.
You guys have plans. huh?
I'll get out of your way.
- No.
- No. no. no.
Stay.
You need cheering up.
and have I got
the movie for you.
Movie night.
I'll get the popcorn.
- Van life Lucy sounds fun.
- You couldn't handle
van life Lucy.
- Oh. look. I'm aware.
She definitely wouldn't
have dated a cop.
- Actually. that time
in my life was mostly bad.
On the bright side. that's what
led me to join the academy.
I think I just wanted
to be that person
I didn't see around me.
somebody who cared.
- And then you got
a training officer
who punished you
for caring too much.
- Yeah. but. you know.
I won in the end.
- Yeah.
Hey. I just got home.
- I know.
I've been watching the security
feed for the last hour.
I ordered you some things.
- Boy. did you.
Flowers. cake. beer.
- Well. I couldn't send myself.
so I ordered some
of your other favorite things.
Well. flowers are really
my favorite thing.
- Well. it was very sweet.
- Aw. I love you.
- I love you too.
Now. it's late over there.
You should get to bed.
- I know.
But first.
we're gonna eat cake together.
Oh. baby.
They were out of chocolate?
- Damn it.
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today